<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[infj]]></title><description><![CDATA[A simple tech blog.]]></description><link>https://alamgirqazi.github.io/infj</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 11:33:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[INFJ Tip 3]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tip 3 Stay strong. Being an INFJ can be very difficult and stressful at times. There will be parts of your life where you feel extremely…]]></description><link>https://alamgirqazi.github.io/infj/tips/3/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alamgirqazi.github.io/infj/tips/3/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h3&gt;Tip 3&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay strong. Being an INFJ can be very difficult and stressful at times. There will be parts of your life where you feel extremely lonely or you think about all the regrets you have in life. These negative thoughts can hinder you and even pull you down a deep hole. You’ll have to remind yourself that you need to be strong not only for your friends and family but for yourself. As staying alive can be the hardest goal any human might have. Don’t do too much self reflecting. As INFJs tend to think a lot about what is going to happen in the future and what has happened in the past. This can probably run your brain to its grave. Never take out your anger on someone. It’s very rare for some INFJs to lash out at people but we are very emotional people who have a very strong sense of morals and beliefs that we cling on to for life. This is probably the one of the regrets I have personally, no matter how much you want to hurt the other person as equally as they have hurt you, taking your anger out on them isn’t going to relieve how you feel. I think it makes it worse sometimes. Do what you love. This applies especially when you are picking courses or occupations. As INFJ, you already have a lot of s*** happening around you so in my opinion you should pick something that you enjoy that will relieve you of your stress from pesky humans. However, make sure you can make a living out of it as well. Careers involving helping people or arts (painting, writing) always lure us. Don’t grow up too fast. I’m not sure if this is applicable to INFJs but since young, I always wanted to do things on my own and grow up faster. It’s better that you enjoy what is happening in your life right now while you still can before becoming an adult. There is a reason maturing sucks! Know that you are not alone. I’ve always thought that I was the only one that felt this way about issues and no one could see way it was wrong. Since young, I’ve always felt alone. It was only this year that I found out I was an INFJ, I saw that some of the INFJs felt the same way as I did. Just knowing that you are not alone can help.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(this was collected from quora)&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[INFJ Tip 5]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tip 5 When I think of some life tips for myself and those like me , I would think: Stop worrying. I’m always worrying about something. God…]]></description><link>https://alamgirqazi.github.io/infj/tips/5/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alamgirqazi.github.io/infj/tips/5/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h3&gt;Tip 5&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I think of some life tips for myself and those like me , I would think:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stop worrying. I’m always worrying about something. God damn it, there are so many things to worry about in life. Especially when you’re an INFJ who tends to take on the problems of others, but don’t. The more you worry, the less you enjoy life, and the less you can work on the things that worry you. It’s hard, but try to relax, and most INFJs probably do already, but if not, keep a journal. It really helps in understanding and breaking down our inherent complexity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not everyone can be like you. Expectations for INFJ are terrible, because our standards are so high, we are the only ones that can possibly honour them. Whenever anyone disappoints me (happens daily), my best friend would tell me, “Not everyone is perfect like you, Nadia.” and I guess, maybe the problem is that not everyone tries to be, or cares about their actions. So it’s really hard to understand, but people aren’t like us. We prioritise other people, and doing our best, which most other people don’t. This leads to a lot of disappointment, if we keep our expectations of others high. All INFJs struggle with temptation and not doing the right thing, and it’s not realistic to think that everyone else is strong enough to do it like we do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can’t always be perfect in everything and that’s okay! I’m really perfectionistic and pedantic, and this has given me positive and negative things. It’s okay to what the best, or to do your best. But when your best isn’t enough, never yourself up for it. People can’t be the best at everything, and the only person expecting that of us, is ourselves. Don’t feel like your best is not enough, keep trying and appreciate your effort.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Never give up hope, and never let the world harden you. Despite the fact that we are innately hopeful, there are still times that we are get really depressed. This is natural, but never let the world let you down. Being able to empathise with people the way that we do in this cruel world, is nothing short of phenomenal. We should consider ourselves so. We need to keep up the fight. It’s something that actually changes the world for the better. Martin luther king, Mother Teresa, Gandhi, Jesus (Isa), and so many others have had great visions and hard lives, but the world remembers them for that, and for going through with their vision. This is the ONLY thing that keeps the world going around.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please don’t be hard on yourself, INFJs. This fight is worth it. Everything comes when it is meant to, the only thing we can do is do our best to get. There is nothing overemotional/ childish/ over ambitious about you. The world needs people like you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(this was collected from quora)&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[INFJ Tip 4]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tip 4 If you are an INFJ, I’d like to congratulate you first of all, for falling into the category of the rarest of all types (<…]]></description><link>https://alamgirqazi.github.io/infj/tips/4/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alamgirqazi.github.io/infj/tips/4/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h3&gt;Tip 4&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are an INFJ, I’d like to congratulate you first of all, for falling into the category of the rarest of all types (&amp;#x3C;2%). Secondly, be prepared to read what I’m going to tell you-&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LIFE IS HARDEST FOR INFJs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let me frame an example.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you see those long faced street vendors nobody buys anything from?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those senile men and women wistfully living lives, having been kicked out of their own homes by their own off springs?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those kids rummaging through the garbage bins, hoping to find stale leftovers, hoping to not have to sleep with empty stomachs?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of those people in pitiable conditions, in need of a helpful hand?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INFJs care for them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, we care for them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We, literally, have lost our sleeps thinking about others in need. But we are no superheroes. As much as we wish to help, we can’t and this pains us all the more. It was just an example to accentuate the empathetic side of an INFJ. Being INFJs, the sense of pity and kindness comes characteristically to us regardless of how much need we, ourselves, may be in. No wonder, INFJs are dubbed as THE UNICORNS-The rarest and the most precious beings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coming to the actual answer, having experienced myself being an INFJ, I’d like the fellow members to ponder the following points as tips -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let go - You can’t control everything around you. People can be vile, cruel, cunning, avaricious, overly pessimistic and depressed. It is NOT your duty to help them all. Just because you are altruistic, kind and optimistic, it doesn’t make you responsible for saving others. Help those you can, WITHOUT HAVING TO DROWN YOURSELF. Stay away from pessimistic people - Although we are inherently optimistic, we are susceptible to fall in depression through the negative influence of others on us. CHASE THEM AWAY! Don’t let any kind of influence have a degrading effect on your otherwise charming personality. Educate yourself on INFJ DOORSLAM - This is actually true. It does exist. We have a tendency to permanently drive people away from our lives when felt exploited or unfairly used. This actually comes as a surprising part to our personality since we, as empaths, are expected to be givers and not haters. But INFJ DOORSLAM makes it sure to make an INFJ badass inside a sweetass. Realize this part of yours before you permanently lose a loved one who may inadvertently have broken your heart. Money is an essential part of life - I can attest to the fact that how much we, INFJs, despise the authority money has in our lives. We would rather pursue an artistic career that pays us peanuts than having to lose our creativity and become millionaires. We have a natural inclination toward art and beauty. Money does indeed hold little or no value. But then again, there is rent to pay, phone and electricity bills subtly crawl through the gap under the front door every month and not to forget, taxes! So, being financially secure should not be compromised. Pursue something that restores your creativity, at the same time pays you well. I assume, these points should suffice for now. Be a balanced INFJ and live life as it is meant to be lived.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(this was collected from quora)&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[INFJ Tip 1]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tip 1 Dear INFJ, I know it’s difficult. Being in the world is very difficult. Existing is very difficult. I know you always look forward to…]]></description><link>https://alamgirqazi.github.io/infj/tips/1/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alamgirqazi.github.io/infj/tips/1/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h3&gt;Tip 1&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dear INFJ,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know it’s difficult. Being in the world is very difficult. Existing is very difficult. I know you always look forward to running away from everything, from everyone, maybe from yourself. I know you are looking for something bigger, something beyond all what you know or everyone know. I know nothing will satisfy you in the dust and ashes of this world. So, dear, look for it. Always remember that you were gifted to see what is beyond, what is beyond the material, what is beyond the language, what is beyond the looks, the gestures, the laughs and tears of the people you meet. Look for that thing that is so deep in the core of your soul that you know could take you above and beyond this world. Always look for the meaning, always analyze and inhale the wisdom of your intuition. And love, love unconditionally, love until you find someone who can love you unconditionally, and you two can hold your hands and dream about eternity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Being in this world is very difficult, being in control is very difficult, being responsible of your enlightenment gift is very very difficult, that’s why sometimes you will screw things up, you will fail, you will be in conflict with yourself, your values, your aspirations of yourself, so don’t be sad, don’t be angry at yourself. It’s true that you are the prophet, the magician, the wise, but still you are a human, so always remember you are a human, you are not perfect, dear, you are trying, and you will be doing your best, and you will be rewarded for that, but sometimes you will just be weak and undetermined, and it’s OK. You will rise up again. Be patient, you are still very young, your existence is very young comparing to the age of the universe, so it takes time to learn, it takes time to be able to fix yourself, to fill the gaps and answer the difficult questions. To learn to love the world as well, to enjoy yourself with its joys, even the sensual ones, they are good as well, they are part of the experience, it’s OK to just let go and have fun from time to time, it is part of your individuation process. Love your self, dear. You really deserve to be loved. I know that from the bottom of my heart. And I love you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(this was collected from quora)&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[INFJ]]></title><description><![CDATA[INFJ INFJ (Introverted, Intuitive, Feeling, Judging)
this blog post covers alot of INFJ related stuff which a true INFJ would agree with…]]></description><link>https://alamgirqazi.github.io/infj/all/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alamgirqazi.github.io/infj/all/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h3&gt;INFJ&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INFJ (Introverted, Intuitive, Feeling, Judging)
this blog post covers alot of INFJ related stuff which a true INFJ would agree with from the core of his heart. This is also for better understanding an INFJ.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INFJs are deeply emotional individuals, although they may not show it constantly. They care very strongly about others and feel emotions on a powerful level. When they care about someone they devote much of their lives to making them happy. INFJs rarely spend time tending to their own needs, often dedicating their lives to the needs of others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INFJs are guided by a deeply considered set of personal values. They are intensely idealistic, and can clearly imagine a happier and more perfect future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INFJs want a meaningful life and deep connections with other people. They do not tend to share themselves freely but appreciate emotional intimacy with a select, committed few. Although their rich inner life can sometimes make them seem mysterious or private to others, they profoundly value authentic connections with people they trust.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like a rose, INFJs have many layers. They will probably not reveal all those layers to you right away. However, the longer you are in an INFJ’s life — and if an INFJ trusts you — the more petals you will discover, all the while moving further inward toward the core of the INFJ’s true self. Sometimes even INFJs don’t fully understand themselves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INFJs often appear quiet, caring and sensitive, and may be found listening attentively to someone else’s ideas or concerns. They are highly perceptive about people and want to help others achieve understanding. INFJs are not afraid of complex personal problems; in fact, they are quite complex themselves, and have a rich inner life that few are privy to. They reflect at length on issues of ethics, and feel things deeply. Because Counselors initially appear so gentle and reserved, they may surprise others with their intensity when one of their values is threatened or called into question. Their calm exterior belies the complexity of their inner worlds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because INFJs are such complex people, they may be reluctant to engage with others who might not understand or appreciate them, and can thus be hard to get to know. Although they want to get along with others and support them in their goals, they are fiercely loyal to their own system of values and will not follow others down a path that does not feel authentic to them. When they sense that their values are not being respected, or when their intuition tells them that someone’s intentions are not pure, they are likely to withdraw.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As an INFJ, I am naturally drawn to people who will open up to me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the most part, I love hearing about the intricate details of peoples’ lives: their fears, their childhood, and their relationships. I enjoy the process of challenging people, and helping them self-actualise. Or, as my friends say, I am a ‘people-fixer’.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like other INFJs, I protect myself from people who will abuse this part of me. And I do it by ‘slamming the door’. What you might not know about your INFJ is that they have probably been burnt by a lot of people they cared deeply for. They gave too much, to a toxic person. The tendency to love selflessly is, unfortunately abused far too often, so your INFJ has developed a mechanism to screen out this pain, and the people likely to inflict it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INFJs are “old souls.” They grow up feeling far wiser than would be predicted by their chronological age. Some may experience themselves as wiser than their teachers or parents. They may take on the role of counseling and advising their friends and siblings, or even their adult family members, from an extraordinarily young age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They tend to feel happiest and most fulfilled when helping and enlightening others through their insights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;many will come to see them as psychic or prophetic, or at least highly perceptive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INFJs feel profoundly misunderstood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INFJs, do you feel like people rarely “get” you? When you start to talk about something you care about, do you notice others failing to grasp why it really matters? If so, you’re not alone. Many INFJs feel deeply misunderstood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INFJs have amazing long-range forecasting abilities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes INFJs may feel like prophets or fortune-tellers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, INFJs are not actually psychic. They see what could be — not necessarily what will happen with absolute certainty. But mature INFJs have honed their forecasting abilities well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INFJs are sometimes called the “extroverted introverts.” They get this nickname because they can be passionate, enthusiastic, and talkative when they are in the presence of someone they feel comfortable with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INFJs know a lot about people. hey get into other people’s heads and figure out what makes them tick.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They often know when someone is lying even to themselves. INFJs are not consciously aware of how they know so much about other people, and they rarely reveal the depth of their knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INFJs tend to be great listeners because they truly care about other people. Likewise, they enjoy helping others understand their emotions and grow. They’re nicknamed “the Counselor” for a reason.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You want to know what’s REALLY going on in people’s lives, not just trivial stuff like what they did this weekend or what they bought on their latest shopping trip. You want to dig deep and get at the things that no one else sees. What does the person in front of you really think? How does this person really feel? The fake facade they put up for other people doesn’t fool you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can be both incredibly shy, quiet, and withdrawn, as well as charming, fun, and hilarious. It’s all about the situation, your mood and energy levels, but most importantly, the people you’re with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When someone comes to you with a problem, you usually don’t give them advice or your opinion unless they ask. Instead, you ask them questions to help them better understand the situation and their own feelings about it. Sometimes you tell a story of a time when something similar happened to you, in the hope that they’ll draw their own lesson. You feel like you can usually see the path they should take, but you don’t want them to do it just because you told them to — you want it to be their decision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even though you may look like you have it together on the outside, you’re extremely sensitive inwardly, and you’re especially sensitive to other people’s words and actions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes you try so hard to make other people happy that you forget to make yourself happy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You almost always have this sinking feeling like you could be doing better with your life. This results in you constantly have secret self-improvement projects going on, like learning how to cook healthy meals, setting better boundaries, or getting better at articulating yourself. Sometimes you push yourself too hard as you attempt to achieve your “perfect” life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You care deeply about the people in your life, but they’ll probably never know just how much you care, because you keep your feelings mostly to yourself. You can have trouble articulating your emotions, even though you feel them intensely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, inspiring others to reach their potential doesn’t mean that INFJs are immune to having their own problems. In fact, some INFJs may become so preoccupied with other people’s feelings that they forget to check in with their own needs. This can lead to INFJs neglecting their own problems and feeling burned out and unhappy. When INFJs do realize they’ve left some issues simmering on the back burner, they may turn to others for guidance and direction. But INFJs might be disappointed when the people they turn to can’t offer the same level of insight that INFJs can give to others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INFJs see two people in everyone. They see the public persona, the outer shell, which everyone else sees. But more important, their Ni provides a deeper sense or impression of people, penetrating appearances and revealing hidden motives and intentions. Consequently, INFJs often feel they can see people more clearly than those people can see themselves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INFJ Confidants are dreamers whose relational genius and caring nature inspire others to achieve great things. INFJs are catalysts for growth in others. Their greatest contribution is their ability to connect with the essence of others and to identify their strengths.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like the INFP, the INFJ can struggle with depression. This may stem from feeling chronically unheard, useless, or misunderstood, as well as from dissatisfaction with INFJ careers or INFJ relationships. Because Ni perceives the world so differently and profoundly, INFJs often experience a sense of loneliness and isolation, even when they are with other people. Depression may also arise from feeling that their ideals and insights are not being recognized or actualized in the world. They may see the world as deaf to, or unconcerned with, the truths they espouse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INFJs define love in terms of emotional intimacy and shared values. They have a great need for connection while at the same time they yearn for solitude. They enjoy one-on-one interaction where they can focus on the other person and really get to know them. Of all the 16 types, INFJs are the most private and the hardest to get to know. Although they enjoy being a mystery, they also long to be known and understood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INFJs seek work that is meaningful and creates growth. They are industrious and quietly enthusiastic. While they are highly idealistic and visionary, they are also task-oriented and intense. They must have goals and are very structured about achieving them. INFJs have extremely high expectations of themselves and sometimes others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INFJs love to learn. Their whole existence is wrapped around growth. They are on a constant quest to improve and untangle more questions. They are gifted at deciphering the connections and profound meaning of things. They are interested in theoretical and abstract concepts that can be applied to people and relationships.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Typical INFJ Strengths
Good at listening
Excellent verbal and written communication skills
Warm, affirming and encouraging
Honors commitments
Insightful
Possible INFJ Weaknesses
Has trouble with conflict
Difficulty receiving criticism
Withdrawn
Holds back
How to attract INFJs
Be a complete mystery that is in desperate need of solving. Be a contradiction and continuously throw them off, they will feel compelled to figure out just what is going on with you. Speak in metaphors and bring up interesting and in depth topics. Be kind but somewhat wounded, so that they feel the need to shelter you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INFJ: Be one big, walking paradox. Look them deep in the eyes and tell them that you ‘Need them’ to help figure yourself out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INFJ: A good long laugh with a friend they can be silly with and possibly some time outdoors/in nature.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[INFJ Tip 2]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tip 2 It’s okay to love yourself as much as you love everyone else. Have self-respect. Don’t feel like you’re inconveniencing people when…]]></description><link>https://alamgirqazi.github.io/infj/tips/2/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://alamgirqazi.github.io/infj/tips/2/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h3&gt;Tip 2&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s okay to love yourself as much as you love everyone else. Have self-respect. Don’t feel like you’re inconveniencing people when you ask for help. It’s the right thing to do and they will understand. It’s okay to say no. Don’t waste your life worrying about the world’s problems. They’re not your fault and you can’t solve them yourself anyway. You are a sensitive one, and it is best to keep yourself out of situations or relationships where you will be overwhelmed or have your heart broken. Live in the moment occasionally. You’ll see how much more you enjoy experiences that way. Just be yourself and you will make friends, I promise you. Don’t waste your time trying to someone else, because you’ll see it doesn’t pay off in the long run. Find a job you love. This one goes for every personality type, but especially INFJs, you will not like life if you’re not passionate about what you’re doing. Try to see the big picture, but not too much. You have a tendency to be perfectionistic, and you’ll find the little details really don’t matter very much in the end. However, existential crises don’t really change your life, keep in mind. Whether or not everyone else’s brains are controlled by starfish, you still have to act like they’re people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(this was collected from quora)&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>